(Amy:)I feel so bad
about lying to Sheldon.
(Amy:)How am I gonna make it up to him?
(Bernadette:)I'd tell you what I do with Howard,
(Bernadette:)but I don't think dressing up
like a Catholic schoolgirl
(Bernadette:)is gonna work with Sheldon.
(Leonard:)He'd probably give you homework.
(Amy:)-Did you lie to Howard about tonight?
-Of course.
(Amy:)And you don't feel guilty about it?
(Bernadette:)Between Penny's gorilla movie
and Howard's gorilla mother,
(Bernadette:)I had no choice.
(Leonard:)Thankfully, Penny and I have
a relationship based on honesty.
(Leonard:)What?
I don't lie to her.
(Bernadette:)Oh, we know you don't lie to her.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Hey, maybe the answer to your
career question is in one of these.
(Sheldon:)Penny, there's only one cookie
with something in the middle
(Sheldon:)that solves life's problems,
and that's an Oreo.